



Phone

+963 937 731 517



E-mail

a.jabban2000@gmail.com



Address

Damascus, Syria



Portfolio

<u>abdulrahman-aljabban.github.io/</u> <u>portfolio</u>



SKILLS

Laravel	90%
PHP	90%
MySQL	80%
System analysis	80%
RESTful API	80%
ООР	80%
HTML & CSS	75%
Jira Agile	80%
Git	90%
MS Office	70%



LANGUAGE

Arabic: Mother tongue

English: Reading

Writing Speaking

ABDUL-RAHMAN AL-JABBAN

BACK-END WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

Hello! I'm Abdul-Rahman Al-Jabban, a back-end web developer. My passion and dedication to my work, during my year of expertise, enabled me to have enough experience and helped me acquire the skills and knowledge necessary to make the project I work on a success. Moreover, I use S.O.L.I.D principles and Repository pattern to come out with a professional, clean, and readable code.



EDUCATION



Technical Computer College

2020 - Present

Damascus University, Syria

Department of Software Engineering

The graduation project was a Health care Web Application that Digitize hospitals data and configured an api for a pill reminder mobile application.



WORK EXPERIENCE



Laravel Software Developer

2022/07 - Present

Limitless Group | Syria

- I made a CV maker Web Application including analyzing the project and making its database and building APIs for the front-end.



Laravel Software Developer

2021/10 - 2022/07

InSoft-Online | Germany

- I made a Time Tracking Web Application including analysing the project and making it's database and design.
- I made a task management web application including analysing the project and making it's database.
- I configured an API for Mobile store application.
- I configured an API for a booking system.

SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

PHPstorm	VS Code
Github	Jira
SQL Server	PHPmyAdmin
Postman	Xampp/Wamp
MS Teams	Windows